[Music]
[Applause]
Hallelujah
um we we bless the
Lord we give him all the
glory we are creatures of mercy and
Grace that is what uh has made us to be
who we are and we bless God for the open
doors in the
Nations I don't con consider
myself the most anointed the most
deserving but by the favor of God is the
one who opens doors he qualifies the
disqualified he lifts them that uh he
uses the things that don't look like so
that he can disapprove those like look
like and I'm so honored to be here it
was a long time outside which I really
needed once in a while he keep to ask
yourself whether this is the Church of
Jesus or the Church of Pastor T and I
realize that this is the Church of Jesus
because even in our
absence the Church of Jesus still
continued I want to congratulate all of
you
for um staying
planted every day I was watching online
and I was very encouraged seeing people
just coming to church knowing that the
senior pastor is not around but knowing
that Jesus is in the house it is an
encouragement I want to appreciate all
the pastors for their
[Applause]
labors all the members for their
commitment and I give Jesus All the
Glory
Hallelujah um I'm confident and certain
if the Lord God was to call me to Glory
Life Church will still continue I am not
going anywhere but I'm just saying I'm
confident and certain that even if the
Lord was to call me to Glory that this
work will not end praise the
Lord uh I remember greetings from
America greetings from the UK the Lord
is doing a wonderful job there and
and great and effective doors have
really
opened I remember it was in one night
when I couldn't sleep and the Lord began
to put a burden and give me the word for
the day and the Word was I am releasing
a new
sound I am releasing a new
sound but I want us to take some time uh
just some few minutes before I want to
lay the foundation for prayer and then
we are going to pray today is our open
Heaven Sunday so I will just lay the
foundation and then we are going to pray
but the first thing that I want us to do
is to create an environment for the
reception of the word of God and this
morning the Lord was very categorical he
was just speaking and he was speaking to
me and telling me let this be the
morning where my children will plead for
Mercy let this be the morning where my
children will plead for mercy
Mercy is what suspends
judgment Mercy is what suspends
judgment the real of the spirit can be a
little bit
legalistic uh I was asking the Lord why
is it that in our many
declarations sometimes we find very few
implementation one declarations are very
powerful because when you keep
quiet it means whatever dominates the
real of the spirit becomes a verdict
over your life if you keep quiet and
there is no utterance from your mouth
whatever dominates the real of the
spirit becomes a verdict over your life
I was watching a clip and I saw a man he
was in a barrier in this land and I
watched a man he took the microphone and
he be began you know right now there's a
lot of
[Music]
recruitment thank you right now there's
a lot of recruitment
especially in the mountain region where
the elders are looking for events like a
barrial and they are coming in and they
begin to
speak evil of the church and they will
come and say you know this is a white
jesus all those manner of things and I
saw this man with a microphone and he
was blaspheming Jesus and and and and
and something came in my spirit because
he even shouted and said that if this
Jesus is there let him kill me now and
then he laughed and but there he didn't
die and I felt like asking Lord why are
you not killing this man and the Lord
spoke to me and he said because there is
no authoriz ation from the real of man
and he said I can do nothing in the real
of men until there is a legal
authorization by them that dwell in that
real and I realized if a man had risen
in that meeting to announce and say from
today I declare 7 days from now you're a
dead man that word would have been
implemented so the Lord was waiting for
legal authorization so that the matter
can be settled that's why the Bible says
that my anger is about to come in the
real of men but I have found no man in
the Gap either to intervene or intercept
or even give me legal authorization to
do what I'm supposed to do is someone
hearing me so when we begin to enter
prayers of Declaration one of the things
is that by declaration automatically
there is
cancellation because when I declare I am
blessed I have already canceled curses
when I declare I am healthy I have
canceled diseases when I declare I
cannot die I have canceled death so when
we begin to enter the dimension of
Declaration in the midst of Declaration
we are already doing a spiritual
operation of
canulation but now the problem is
whatever gives your utterance Authority
is the status of your being the Bible
says and Hezekiah received a verdict
from Zion that indeed you're are going
to die and this is the prophet of God
this is a man that was refutable when it
comes to releasing prophetic decrees so
Isaiah was not lying Isaiah was not
bringing a rumor he was bringing the
true word of God but the man stood
contended for his soul not because of
anything he began to pray from a place
of his work and I discovered there are
negotiations in the spirit we cannot
Prevail in until Mercy is deployed upon
a generation Psalms verse 30 Psalms 30
and verse 5 Psalms 30 and verse5 we are
about to invoke Mercy somebody say Mercy
somebody say Mercy in the economy of
help there are various factors that act
as an advantage for the help of man one
of them that is released from the
quarters of Eternity one of the Divine
backups that come to help man is the
system called
Mercy the Bible says for his anger is
just but for a
moment his favor is for Life weeping may
endure for a night but joy comes in the
morning I want us to focus on the part
that says for his anger is just but
please talk to me this morning for his
anger is just but for a that tells me
God can be angry Psalms 30 was written
by David at after doing the census he
was warned not to not to count Israel by
counting Israel he was communicating to
the Lord that the people belong to him
because the culture of counting
something was the culture of a shepherd
and the shepherd had authority to count
what he possessed so any time a Shepherd
went to count his animal it was a
language that this was his possession is
someone getting me so now you have your
100 sheep and before they come back you
begin to count them now Israel was not
the flock of David Israel was the flock
of the Lord the second thing the reason
why David was counting Israel it was to
identify the men that could handle the
sword the men that could handle the
sword so that tells me he was relying on
the abilities of his armies but not the
ability of the Deliverance of Yahweh so
he comes and counts Israel one mistake
that he makes he's communicating to God
that now Israel belongs to him he was
just an entrusted Shepherd who was
entrusted with the mandate to lead the
people the same way there are many
things the Lord has entrusted us with
but they don't belong to us we are just
custodians of his Mysteries we are
custodians of his assignment the second
thing the Bible says he counted the men
that could handle the sword meaning that
he was trying to look at his military
ability this was to communicate to God
that the Lord was no longer their Helper
and he was no longer their deliverer the
Bible says there are men that trust in
chariots and some trust in horses but we
trust in the name of the Lord so the
trust of David was no longer in the help
of God as the god that fight his battle
and so when he counted Israel the Lord
came in judgment and he came and
announced there are three possibilities
either my sword Moves In the Land either
there is vermine or I perpetually allow
your enemies to pursue you these are
dimensions of God's judgment he was
angry at David he came and said David
there are three options the sword for
judgment the second option is that your
enemies will perpetually pursue you
that's a very dangerous thing and the
third thing is that now I will begin to
move in the territory and and the Lord
was announcing judgment but David looked
upon the mountains of Zion he pleaded
for mercy and that's where as Psalms 30
comes in he says oh God your anger your
anger oh God is just but for a moment
this morning I'm here to remind somebody
the anger of the Lord is just but for a
moment there are things we may have done
because today I want us to pray from a
place of Freedom Hallelujah anything
that stand on your way must be lifted
today and that's why we must begin to
cry for the economy of mercy and then
David writes and says morning may endure
for a night because the sin brings
darkness in our lives but there is hope
for a new dawn this language of morning
may endure for a night it has nothing to
do with afflictions that are happening
in your life just like that these are
afflictions because of the Judgment of
God
darkness is now permitted to wover over
my life because judgment has begun to
count over my life but David is saying
no matter the darkness of the hour Lord
I know there is a system called Mercy
Hallelujah I know there is a system
called Mercy some of us have been a
place of Darkness you have never enjoyed
the joy of your salvation may this be
the day where the economy of Mercy will
be deployed upon your life may this be
the service Where Mercy will say no
where judgment was meant to Prevail let
Mercy begin to say no in one minute
begin to commune with the father open up
your mouth and begin to cry begin to
tell the Lord Lord yes I know we are
still in the world of sin we are still
in a place where we are subjected to
failure begin to render your heart the
Bible says in the Book of Job the Lord
came upon the people he said I am no
longer interested with the lips and the
service of your lips but I'm interested
with the rendering of your hearts in the
Old Testament anytime the men wanted to
pray they will tear their garments but
the Lord was saying it is possible to
have torn garments but we don't have
torn Hearts this morning my father we
are not just rendering our garments we
are rendering our hearts we are
rendering our hearts where we have
fallen short of your glory where we have
missed the mark where we have entered
into error where we have offended you
where we have put your name into shame
where we have slumbered where oh God we
have opened door spiritually remember
Mercy remember Mercy Jehovah God
remember Mercy remember Mercy we came to
transa with the throne remember Mercy
let our Darkness not consume us let
Darkness not Prevail over us the Bible
says morning may endure for a night let
our Day Break Forth let the day of Li
let the time of light let the time of Li
let it break forth let the time of light
let it break forth father take away
every crown of judgment let thy mercy
let thy mercy the Bible declares you are
mercies on you every morning your
mercies on you every morning Lord this
is the system of help this is the system
of help we are limited without Mercy we
are incapacitated without Mercy we are
victims of judgment without Mercy but
this morning my father on the first day
of the month of December we are taking
away every legality we are taking away
every ground we are taking away every
Foundation we are taking away everything
that may hinder us doing business with
the
throne remember Mercy Lord somebody
begin to compel begin to cry for Mercy
begin to cry for Mercy our lives are
lives of repentance we live repentant
lives in our walk we may have missed it
in our speech we may have missed it in
our conduct we may have missed it we may
have be found in areas that are not
pleasing unto our father let this be the
day of Mercy as we begin the month of
December let Mercy Prevail let Mercy
Prevail this is the economy that brings
help to man this is the help of
[Music]
man mercies of God let the mercies of
God Prevail over our lives Prevail over
our families Prevail of our children
Lord let thy mercy let thy mercy Prevail
Even in our land even in this church
Mercy Mercy Lord Mercy Lord Mercy Lord
Mercy Lord Mercy Lord Mercy Lord Mercy
Mercy Mercy Lord let the sword of
judgment if I fall let me fall in thy
hands if I fall let me fall in thy hands
uh let the enemies not pursue us let the
sword of judgment not come upon us Lord
Mercy Mercy where we have errored where
we have missed Mark where we have
offended you when David sinned he said
oh God now I have empowered your enemies
against you where we have empowered your
enemies against you we repent we repent
my father somebody render your
heart render thy heart before the
presence of the Living God confess for
your speech confess for your conduct
confess for the weakness in the flesh
confess for the moments you have been
falling and failing let Mercy Prevail
let Mercy Prevail let Mercy Prevail let
Mercy Prevail let Mercy prevail
[Music]
you are a holy God You Are Holy oh
Father You Are Holy we acknowledged by
the ranking and status of your being in
our nature we may not have communion but
today Purge us Purge us cut every branch
that doesn't bear fruit circumcise every
flesh Li
[Music]
let Mercy
Prevail let thy mercy Prevail let your
mercy Prevail let the morning come to an
end let us enter into our new door let
us enter into the brightness of the day
sh
[Music]
you
thank you for
youry Lord I'm
amaz how you show me
Mery than
him thank you for
youry Lord I'm my
face but how you show me
mer thank you for your
mercy Lord I
by how you show me mer Mercy is our
divine
Advantage thank
you there is helping
[Music]
Mery let Mercy speak over my
life let Mercy speak over my
family let Mercy speak Life Church let
Mercy speak over Kya
[Music]
she
I am a
master I am
am I
am am
God thank you thank
you am
a sh
God oh God
oh God
oh God oh Jesus thank you God
oh
God she
thank somebody ping the Holy
Ghost there is a system called
Mercy there is a system called
[Music]
Mercy we can never have divine counters
if men are not conscious of the mercies
of God we can never do business in the
glory Dimension if men are not conscious
of the mercies of God this is what kept
Israel this is what kept Israel they
kept on acknowledging that oh God you
are mercy endureth forever your are
mercy endureth
forever look at the book of 2 Chronicles
2 Chronicles chapter number
7 2 Chronicles chapter number
sh when Solomon had finished praying
fire came down from heaven and consumed
the burnt offering and the
sacrifices and the glory of the Lord
filled the
Temple look the second next next verse
and the priest could not enter to the
house of the Lord because the glory of
the Lord had filled the Lord's
House look when all the children of
Israel saw how the fire came down and
the glory of the Lord of the temple they
bowed their faces to the ground on the
pavement see how they worshiped and
worshiped and praised the Lord saying
for he is good for his mercy endureth
forever they understood if God has to
move in our midst it's not because of
our righteousness it is because of his
Mercy because if God has to move if he
has to move and still preserves us it
takes
Mercy when they saw the cloud and they
saw the glory in the temple they bowed
down and worshiped and said he is good
and his mercy endureth forever the
Encounters of God they do not happen
because there they don't happen because
of our giving they don't happen because
we are the best they happen because the
Mercies of God have suspended
judgments I was asking the Lord Lord why
is it that you we are praying but
there's no power in our prayer why is it
that we are not seeing the glory again
he said because man is coming from a
place of confidence not a place of
Brokenness he's saying there is an
uprightness on the altar that cannot
permit my power to penetrate I am the
Lord that operates in Broken Vessels but
there is a much wholeness on my altar I
only deal with vessels that can lie on
the altar if the Holy Ghost looks and
seeks a yielded vessel that's a vessel
he can move in and I began to ask Lord
what happened to the glory of your house
he said son when Holiness left my house
my Holy Spirit also left because
Holiness and holy spirit operate in the
same equation and when we began to talk
of prosperity our Di declarations are in
vain until the protocols are
restored we can declare every scripture
but the power of the scripture is in the
authority of our
[Music]
Holiness I was watching a man of God and
I watched and I saw something and the
Lord began to speak to me told me son
observe the pattern of fashion to
understand the cycles of time so I
looked and I discovered we are going
back to the days of bell bottoms there
is a there is a there is a it's like
there is a resetting of time I don't
know if you've discovered that in the
fashion world because fashion
communicates the timings that we are in
it's like we are going back to the
settings of time it's like we are going
back to the 70s and the 80s that's why
there there are young people there are
young people who are beginning to sing
songs that were done in the 70s and80s
0s and '90s and the Lord began to ask me
look in the spirit and ask yourself what
happened in the' 70s it was Revival what
carried that Revival it was Holiness he
said as it is in the natural the clock
is also shifting in the spiritual Let
the church understand what I am doing in
the spiritual because in the natural men
are trying to position themselves
according to the timings of the 70s
[Music]
there was a genuine love of God in the
70s and ' 80s there was a genuine move
of God in the 70s and ' 80s that men
will gather in a family in a family
group and people will be filled with the
Holy Ghost people will pray in a family
group and healings will happen I met one
of the generals and he told me matters
of healing was not a Sunday Affair it
was a midweek Affair Sunday was for
heavier matters may the Lord restore
those timings but m see must be the
economy we are standing
on the Bible says the temple curtains
were turned into two so that every man
can go and do business with the throne
but the Bible did not say that the
Priestly protocol was Tor into two the
levitical order of meeting a holy God is
that you needed to observe Holiness and
most the Lord was very specific on
sexual Purity there was a protocol to
enter the holies of holies the high
priest needed to wear undergarments and
the Lord had to interrogate the
cleanness of the undergarments there was
a protocol for the shakina to fall in
the altar there was a protocol We Are
ushering Men where they cannot stand
that is a place of death that's why our
prayers are in vain we are making
declarations prophetic pronunciations
but in the reals of the spirit these are
just grammar and English whatever gives
back up to our wording is our sture in
the spirit we can quote all scripture
and go home empty but there is a word
you can speak with the right posture and
that word becomes a reality I refuse to
come to church and just come and make
declaration and leave empty Hallelujah
let Mercy speak of Our Lives Psalms 136
verse 1 to4 this was a whole Psalm to
remind Israel that everything in their
life was out of Mercy they cried a whole
s
just declaring the mercy of God just
look at it is a whole Psalm is a very
long Psalm oh give thanks to the Lord
for he is good for his Mercy endures
forever look at two oh give thanks to
the god of gods for his Mercy endures
forever look at three oh give thanks to
the Lord of lords for his mercies
endures forever look at four to him who
alone does great wonders for his Mercy
endures forever look at five to him who
by wisdom made the heavens for his Mercy
endures forever look at six is a whole
sum of Mercy to him who laid down the
Earth above the waters for his mercies
does what endures forever look at seven
to him who made great light for his
Mercy the man is talking about creation
but he's saying the backing power of
every activity of God was his
Mercy even speak of the Deliverance out
of
Egypt look at
to the Sun to Rule the Day for his Mercy
endure forever he continues to the Moon
he continues it's a Longs is a sum of
Mercy today we came to plead for Mercy
oh Lord anything that may hinder our
interaction it's not an open Heaven Lord
if you cannot show up it is not an open
Heaven Lord if there are legalities on
the ground Zechariah Chapter number 3
and verse one let's just look at this
Zariah chapter number 3 and verse one we
are just dealing with legality so that
we can pray hallelujah hallelujah
there's a lot of uprightness in the
spirit men men are coming to God and
they have ignored who he is he is
Holy he is Holy he is Holy he's
[Music]
holy sh
he is Holy CU there is no one else who
is faithful and true Only You Are
[Music]
Holy but
true oh my
[Music]
life is a
test only you
are only you are worthy Lord only you
are
worthy only you wonderful to me only you
Wonder oh there
[Applause]
there like
you who is faithful Lord who is
Faith true
my love my heart my
heart
heart my
love is a
test oh for there no
one there is no one
there like
you who is faithful
oh my love my heart oh my life my
heart my
life is
a
Zariah chapter number three I want us to
take away every legality that might
hinder our transaction in prayer
Hallelujah there is a real in the
spirit the more you grow in
God the more you understand that there
is a real where the enemy meets you from
legal
Dimensions there is a real where the
enemy applies
legality that's why when we look at this
scripture which we're going to look at
we will understand there are levels of
opposition and hindrances that are a
byproduct of open doors and legalities
that we've permitted in our lives is
someone getting me there is a real that
becomes a little bit legal I know Grace
Grace the grace of God will allow you to
transact with God in some Dimensions but
there is a real in the spirit if you
don't Master it it is a real of
legalities and it operates in all
quarters it operates both in the Demonic
Kingdom and in the Kingdom of Light that
is the real where a man can commit one
sin and die it was the real of generals
I I read a book whereby a man of God a
man of God was sent to one another man
of God and he was told to tell the man
of God return to your prophetic Ministry
because I never called you as a teacher
and on that Sunday the man went and
taught and after teaching he got a road
accident and died on the very day
because at that time he had entered a
real of legality you must ask yourself
why is it that Moses receives judgment
just because he refused to talk to a
rock and the man decides to hit a rock
and the next thing the Lord tells him
you cannot enter the promised land what
Lord what is the problem what is the
problem of a man hitting a rock he has
not fornicated he has not killed anyone
but you are putting him in the same
equation as the same people that have
rebelled and worshiped a golden calve
what is the problem with just speaking
to a rock no it is a language of rank
this is Moses according to his level of
operation one mistake is enough to
disqualify him is someone getting me is
someone getting me that's why Samson and
David can commit the same error Samson
loses his eyes loses his hair and he
dies in the midst of the enemies the
Bible says when he said Lord give me
this one more time that I may die with
my enemy enemies and the Lord came the
power of the Lord came and he died with
the very people he was meant to to to
kill he dies with the very enemy that he
was meant to destroy because the
ordination of Samson was a
Nazarite and a Nazarite was supposed to
operate in Holiness for the power of God
to operate David is a king and a
worshipper messes up with another man's
wife in fact the sin of David is greater
because Delilah is a prostitute
but David the only thing that happens a
door is opened and there is chaos in his
home but when he enters into repentance
the Lord restores him he still has the
Holy Spirit he still called The Beloved
because both David and Samson were not
operating on the same rank meaning that
the details of their legalities were
different in our own homes the way you
punish your 2-year-old is not how you
deal with your
5-year-old is that true because the
5-year-old has entered a rank where you
know there are things that you ought not
to do but there is Mercy of a 2-year-old
but there is a level you cannot show
Mercy to a
5-year-old and that's why we must take
every legality irrespective of our
rank Zachariah the Bible says then he
showed me
Joshua the high priest standing before
the angel of the Lord let's all
read and Satan standing at his right
hand to do what oppose him we want to
deal with the legality that might lead
to opposition to your prayer tell your
neighbor neighbor we didn't come to
waste time we came to transact with Zion
and every legal ground must be lifted at
this hour Hallelujah I am tired of
declaring words and they fall on empty
ground because there is legality to
oppose I read the book of Martin
Luther and he said he wrote he said my
life was a repentant life and in one of
the captions he writes and says there is
nothing the devil hates like a man that
lives a life of
repentance because any time he's rising
in legality to attack he realizes the
man has created a Channel of
Mercy he said there is nothing that the
devil hates as a man that lives a life
of repentance because every time the
enemy is waiting to strike when he's
coming he realizes there is no ground
for my
entry then he showed me Joshua the high
priest standing before the angel of the
Lord and Satan standing at his right
hand to oppose
him and the Lord said to Satan the Lord
rebuke you Satan the Lord who has chosen
Jerusalem rebuke you is this not a brand
plucked from the
fire now Joshua was clothed with filthy
garments and was standing before the
angel then he answered and spoke to
those who stood before him saying take
away the filthy garment from him and to
him he said see I have removed iniquity
from you and I'll cloth you with the
rich robs let me just have something so
that I can show you what we about to
pray let me just have a sh just bring it
bring that that massai cover just bring
it let me show you something we are not
coming to tell the we are not we are not
coming with our strength we are coming
to receive the strength of God listen
just cover yourself the Bible says the
man was covered with filthy rags are you
getting it are you getting it and the
devil stood opposite to oppose him so
this man cannot transact with Heaven
because there is a legality of filthy
racks now listen the efforts of this man
cannot take away the
racks many of us have tried to survive
by our effort you want to repent and
then you go for seven days that's effort
there is a called
surrender this is a man that is now
surrendered to God and the Lord must
release an angel just come the Lord must
release an angel to take away take away
take away it is not by might nor by
power it will take the spirit of the
Lord to uncover anything it's not by
your ability it will take the grace of
God to take away every Garment of
filthiness that has been hindering your
operation in the real of the spirit is
someone getting me I am not here to flip
your guilt the Bible says there is now
no condemnation to anyone that is in
Christ Jesus I'm here to remind you that
even with our own abilities we cannot
cleanse ourselves what can take away my
sin nothing but the blood of Jesus it is
not my labors it is not my sacrifice
it's me lifting my hands and saying Lord
I'm just a creature of Mercy whatever
that is upon me that defiles me lift it
up right now when the prodigal came back
home the Bible says he came with fill
the garments the father took away the
Garment and then the next thing he never
left him naked he never left him naked
just come he never let me get another
garment he never left him naked there
has to be another garment Place upon
your life it's called the Garment of
righteousness there has to be a
transaction they they taking away of the
filthy garment and placing upon the
Garment of righteousness it is not your
work it is the work of the Holy Ghost
May the spirit of the Living God begin
to take away every garment that is not
pleasing before his present May the
spirit of the Living God begin to take
away every filthy comment in one minute
begin to make that prayer tell the Lord
Lord I stand in surrender I stand in
surrender my father I stand in surrender
Jehovah you who sees all I can hide from
men I can hide from Pastor I am tired of
men having a good report I am standing
before you omniscient omnipotent
omnipresent God the all knowing god you
who knows the heart the desires of the
heart you who knows me by name you who
has the number of air upon you you has
every detail upon my life today in the
name of Jesus take away every filthy rug
take away every rag whatever gives the
enemy an advantage to stand in my altar
of prayer to oppose me as I pray Lord
take it out Purge me with the high soap
Purge me Jehovah God wash me with your
word take away every Garment of
filthiness take away every garment
somebody begin to make that prayer be
genuine with God we came to our father
let garments begin to drop it is not by
our ability there is a system called
surrender there is a system called
surrender there is a place you know I am
lacking in this area this is the area of
my weakness this is the area of my
disadvantage this is the area Lord
intervene at this hour intervene at this
hour I am tired as a dog that goes back
to its vomit intervene at this hour I am
tired going around in Cycles intervene
at this hour take away the Garment of
field take away the Garment of
pornography the Garment of masturbation
the Garment of sexual perversion the
Garment of greed the Garment of L the
Garment of Pride the Garment oh God that
keeps on defiling my life take it out
take it out Holy Ghost Wash Me wash me
wash me make me whole clean me today
clean me today clean me
[Music]
today surrender to
him we cannot be
opposed in the place of
prayer take away every
legality anything that stands as a
legality let it be taken out of your
life
everything that stands is a legality let
it be taken out of your life your
Authority will be restored your power
will be restored your anointing will be
restored let the garments be taken out
receive the Garment of righteousness
receive it now by faith receive the
covering of righteousness by faith
what can make me whole again nothing but
the blood of
[Music]
Jesus what can make me
all
again nothing but the
blood
Jes
oh
pra is the Lord the blood from
uel white as no
no
other
know nothing but the
blood oh
pre
preious he
the makes me
nothing but the blood of
[Music]
to
you're to
[Music]
for for here I
for for
[Music]
my
son
d
nowk you
Jesus oh my
God the Lord is restoring our
Authority I don't know I just remember
the the lyrics of this song it says on
that day when I meet him I will know him
[Music]
need need
to
to time to
[Music]
thank you Jesus let's go back to that
scripture in
Zachariah he answered and
spoke Zachariah
take away the field the Garment from him
andto him he said see I have removed
iniquity from you and I'll clothe you
with Rich robs I declare in the name of
Jesus everyone under the sound of my
voice the filthy garment has been taken
out and in this service the Lord has
clothed you with Rich robs dipped in the
blood of Emmanuel robs of
righteousness and I want to announce
there is no legality of operation
as you open your mouth today in prayer
your words are l in the real of the
spirit I declare you are Authority in
the spirit has been restored in the
mighty name of
Jesus look at the next scripture quickly
look at it the Bible says and I said let
them put on a tabban on his head so they
put a clean tabban on his head and they
put the cloth on him and the angel of
the Lord stood by Hallelujah there is
divine backup then the angel of the Lord
admonished Joshua
saying that says the Lord of host if you
keep my command then you shall also
judge my house I want to remind you when
we walk in Holiness our Authority in the
spirit is restored the language of
judgment is the language of authority
today there are matters we are going to
judge and because we are dealing from a
place of authority I declare that
judgment shall be established in the
mighty name of Jesus and he said if you
keep my then then you shall also judge
my house and likewise have charge of my
court I will give you place to walk
among these who stand here lift up your
hands in the name of Jesus I declare at
this hour anyone that had lost Authority
in prayer I declare by this scripture
may the Lord restore your Authority I
say by the reality and revelation of
this scripture let your Authority be
restored
your mouth will begin to releasee
arrows your utterance is low your words
in the realm of the spirit are verdicts
in the mighty name of Jesus everyone
that operated with a hijacked mouth I
declare under this anointing may the
Lord restore the power of your
speech every prophetic mouth hijacked
every intercessory mouth hijacked I
release a fresh fire I release of Fresh
Fire I release of Fresh Fire release
receive your sound receive your sound
you will not be silenced your voice will
not be quenched your sound cannot be cut
off in this hour I restore your
soundos the sound of prayer no amount of
warfare will say L lens you no amount of
warfare will make you keep quiet I
release the strength of Zion arise in
war your words are like
[Music]
arrows I don't know who the Lord is
dealing with right now but I sense their
mouth being restored the Bible says oh
Lord in the book of Isaiah I am a man of
unclean lips and the Bible says an angel
carried some tongues went on the altars
of Elohim he picked CS of fire and
patched the mouth of Isiah and from that
time whatever he uted became low in the
land I declare today there is a ping of
prophetic mouths there is a ping of
prophetic mouth they will begin to utter
and matters will come to pass wherever
they are let the fire that punches be
upon your mouth now
every mouth of intercessors that were
being hijacked I restore the sound back
I restore your sound back I restore the
fire on your altar
sh personal Revival let it be upon you
now
[Music]
oh my
God the first thing the enemy will
attack in your life is not your business
the first thing the enemy will attack in
your life is not your family or your
children the first thing the enemy will
attack is not your finances that is the
by product the first thing the enemy
will attack is your prayer life when
your prayer life goes out many other
things will begin to go out today in the
name of Jesus I release a fresh fire for
prayer I release a fresh fire for prayer
where the altars of prayer were attacked
may the Lord rejuvenate you may the Lord
revive you may the Lord revive you may
the Lord revive you in the name of
[Music]
Jesus Somebody Pray in the Holy Ghost
personal Revival Lord I'm coming back to
the Heart of Worship restore the heart
of a worshiper restore the heart of a
worshiper restore my heart to the
quarters where I will cry in the morning
restore my heart to the moments where I
will close my bags and go to the
mountain I am coming back where it is
all about you Jesus restore the fire let
the candle of my spirit let it never go
out restore the fire of prayer restore
the fire of Prayer Revival in my life
personal Revival personal Revival
personal Revival my personal prayer
altar let it catch fire now let it be on
fire let it be on fire Let It Be On
[Music]
Fire
coming heart of wor
when it's all about
you it's all about you
Jesus I'm sorry Lord for the thing I
made it when it's all about
you it's all about you I'm coming back
I'm coming
it's when it's all about it's all about
you
I'm I'm
Sor you
I'm
coming I'm
coming to
the me Lord It's about you I'm
sorry I'm I'm
sorry all
it's all about you it's all about you so
I'm coming
back what is all
about lord it's all about you about I'm
sorry I'm sorry
Lord when I'm
about the things it's all it's all about
you it's all about
you
oh when it's all about you
Jesus oh it's it's not about
me oh it's not about the things you can
give
Lord It's All About You
Jesus it's all about
you yes it's all about you
Lord yes it's all about you
Jesus I'm sorry Lord for the things of
made when it's so and it's all
about Jesus about you it's all
about
Jesus
redeem
my redeem my heart again
[Music]
savior come to shout to me from
sins he you're familiar with my
weakness devoted to the
end
Redeemer
savior
friend say Redeemer
redeem redeem my heart
ofor come and Shout to me you're
familiar you're familiar with my
weakness and still to B to the
Redeemer say
redeem
redeem redeem my heart of you're my
savior come and
Shout you're familiar you're familiar
with my and still Lord your departed to
the
Earth
Redeemer
savior
friend you're familiar with my
weakness and still you're devoted to the
end
oh red
Our Savior
friend Father we bless
you and we give you
glory even as I lay ground for our
prayer
today thank you that there is no
legality thank you for an open Heaven
thank you because in such
atmospheres everything is possible the
sick will be healed them that are in
bondage will be delivered
them that are depressed will be given
hope every matter of battle will be
settled and as we walk out of this tent
it shall be the tent of meetings Lord we
give you honor I declare now open the
hearing ear and open the sing Eye I
arrest the atmosphere the Bible says
that the devorer when the seeds fell on
the ground it was the birds of the air
that came and picked them we declare
nothing will come to pick the word that
is being relayed to us right now this is
light this is life this is instruction
this is Direction this is your voice in
Jesus name we have prayed we can have
our seats
briefly worshippers you can have your
seats briefly let me lay this Foundation
of prayer and then after that we are
going to pray
hallelujah
hallelujah there there is such an
anointing in the
house anything is possible at this
hour when you understand the culture of
receiving